<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.important {
			font-weight: bold;
		}
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>
       
		<font color='#9152a0'><b>
	    We are happy that you have found our website!
 		<br></br><br></br>
		We created this space to communicate to the world what we are about...what we want, what we do, and our progress. Please, explore the tabs on the left to find out more about this new organization that looks out for orphans around the world!
  		<br></br><br></br>
  		There are different ways to get involved with the cause:
  		<UL TYPE="SQUARE">
  			<li>
  			You are an organization devoted to help improving 
  			one or more of the standards we defined of children's life. 
  			Click on "Join -> As an organization" and add your organization to the network
  			for sharing your ideas and projects as well as learning from other organizations.
  			</li>
  			<li>
  			You are an orphanage, a group or an individual that you daily interact with abandoned
  			or orphaned children trying to improve their lifes. By joining our network you
  			can share the needs you have with organizations and individuals that can contribute
  			by creating projects to respond to your needs or supporting your efforts. 
  			Click on "Join -> As an orphange" and share what you are doing with the rest of the world.
  			</li>
  			<li>
			You are an individual that want to make a difference in children's life and help
			the existing efforts either financially or by volunteering. You can search the
			current opportunities and needs around the world by navigating to our map view 
			and looking for the needs and projects helping the cause.
			</li>
			<li>
			You want to know more about the situation of the cause, the current needs and raise
			awareness. You can be informed on a daily news of the situation, search for specific 
			information, meet people that are involved in the cause and share your ideas
			and the information about the cause in social medias. Click on projects, follow them, recommend
			them to friends and share them in Google+ or Facebook.
			</li>
			<li>
			You want to be directly involved and develop further our project trying 
			to facilitate collaboration between organizations and individuals involved in the
			cause of helping orphans and abandoned children. You can join our research team
			in charge of hunting organizations that are part of the cause or organizations that
			may be able to help the cause by providing help in a specific area. We also 
			identify groups of children around the world that need help and do not had the opportunity
			yet of being in touch with the right people. Please, drop us an email and tell 
			us what is your interest and how you would like to help.
			</li>
			<li>
			You are a programmer or a graphical designer willing to help improving our tool facilitating
			the collaboration. You may want to improve our front end or the design of our front end. 
			Our code is an open source because we think that collaboration goes beyond this cause.
			In fact, we hope that other causes benefit of this project to accelerate help in other fields.
			Our source is at https://github.com/mcharcos/owb.git. Follow our project and let
			us know if you feel like contributing in some way. 
			</li>
  		</UL>
  		<br></br><br></br>
		If you have any feedback for us, regarding our site, ideas or approaches, or if you'd like to get involved, we would love to hear from you! Our email is owb@orphanagewithoutborders.org.
  		<br></br><br></br>
		Thank you, and have a good day!!
		</b></font>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 