<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
	<ui:style>
		.important {
			font-weight: bold;
		}
		.description{
	        color:#9152a0;
	        margin: 30px;
	   }
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>
	   <div class="{style.description}">
		
	    <h1>CONTEXT</h1>
	    Abandoned children are a vulnerable population who experience a difficult life. 
	    The population includes orphan children living in the streets as well as children hosted 
	    in orphanages because either they do not have a family or their families are unable to 
	    provide them care due to extreme poverty or other reasons. The number of abandoned 
	    children is increasing worldwide especially in countries striked by <b>poverty</b>, 
	    <b>conflicts</b>, <b>diseases</b> and <b>disasters</b> where the mortality increases
	    as well as their chances of becoming orphans. <br></br>
	    <br></br><br></br>
	    
	    <b>Poverty</b> is the main reason of having a high number of the children in orphanages. 
	    Most of the children in orphanages have not lost their parents but their families do 
	    not afford to raise them. For example, many children born during Ceausescu’s 
	    anti-abortion law were placed in orphanages. According to the Save the Children reports, 
	    an average of 80% of the children in orphanages are put in orphanages due to poverty. 
	    In Ghana, Indonesia and countries in eastern Europe this percentage is even higher: 90%.<br></br>
	    <br></br><br></br>
	    
	    Countries involved in <b>war</b> also have a high number of orphans such as Afghanistan that 
	    has one and half million orphans. Based on Unicef report, “During the last decade, 
	    2 million children worldwide have been killed as a result of war, four to five million 
	    children have been disabled, 12 million have been left homeless, more than one million 
	    orphaned or separated from their parents, and approximately ten million children have 
	    been psychologically traumatized as a result of war (UNICEF's The State of World's 
	    Children 1996)”.<br></br>
	    <br></br><br></br>
	    
	    Epidemic <b>diseases</b> such as HIV are another reason for the increased number of orphans 
	    who in addition are likely to host these diseases. For instance, South Africa, with the 
	    rate of 70,000 a year, has the highest number of orphans with HIV whose parents have 
	    died due to AIDS (Time World June 01 2011). In addition, disease outbreaks that happen 
	    in war countries are difficult to eradicate. For example, polio re-emerged in 2005 in 
	    Angola after the civil war and vaccination campaigns were difficult (especially in the 
	    countryside) to pursue when the infrastructures were destroyed.<br></br>
	    <br></br><br></br>
	    
	    Finally, <b>natural or human made disasters</b> increase the number of orphans. For instance, 
	    in Japan and Haiti, a huge number of children lost their parents due to earthquakes. 
	    It is estimated that 1400 children lost at least one parent, around 200 children lost 
	    both earthquake in Japan (Time World July, 10 2011.) and U.S. adopteted 1000 children 
	    from Haiti. The effects of natural disasters are commonly stronger in poor countries 
	    and increase the chances of diseases. <br></br>
  		<br></br><br></br>
  		<br></br><br></br>
  		<br></br><br></br>
		</div>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 