<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">    
	<g:HTMLPanel>
<div align="center">
<p>&nbsp;</p>
    <font style="font-family:Century Gothic;">
 <font style="font-size: 50px; color: #8BFF2D;">Our mission</font>
 <br></br>
<p><font style="font-size: 22px; color: #F09;">Orphanage Without Borders harvests the power of technology to <strong>connect</strong> and <strong>engage</strong> individuals and resources with the <strong>needs</strong> of orphan children around the world.</font></p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<font style="font-size: 50px; color: #8BFF2D;">Our approach</font>
<font style="font-size: 15px; color: #999;">
  <p>1. We gather and present <strong>knowledge</strong> about the needs of orphan children. </p>
  <p>2. We provide a practical source of <strong>information</strong> for volunteers and organizations, increasing the flow of information. </p>
  <p>3. We facilitate the creation of small tangible <strong>projects</strong> to meet the essential needs of these children. </p>
  <p>4. We <strong>connect</strong> existing resources (organizations, individuals and corporations) to these projects.</p>
  <p>5. We <strong>empower</strong> people to actively participate and make decisions that directly help orphans around the world.</p>
  <p>6. We <strong>visually represent </strong>the projects and resources for anyone who wants to improve the situation.</p>
  <p>7. We foster <strong>collaboration and crowdsourcing</strong> for more efficient results. </p>
  <p>8. We promote the <strong>exchange of ideas and experiences</strong>, bringing donors, organizations and volunteers closer.</p>
  <p>9. We provide <strong>transparency</strong> about the legitimacy of orphanages around the world. </p>
  <p>10. We issue <strong>updates</strong> on the status of projects that are addressing the needs of orphan children. </p>
</font>
</font>
</div>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 