<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
    <ui:with field='res' type='com.owb.playhelp.client.resources.Resources'/>
    
	<ui:style src="../../../resources/GlobalStyles.css">
		.important {
			font-weight: bold;
		}
		.description{
	        color:#9152a0;
	        margin: 30px;
	   }
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>

		
	   <div class="{style.description}">
	    <h1>OUR VIEW</h1>
	    
			<table align="left">
	    		<tr>
			        <td width="570">
					<g:Image url='{res.viewWebPic.getSafeUri.asString}' pixelSize="300,300"/>  
		  		    </td>
	  		    </tr>
	    		<tr>
			        <td width="570">
					Orphanage Without Borders provides a common portal for organization and individuals to 
				    unify their efforts and facilitate contributions to the cause of abandoned children. This site 
				    allows projects of our network to inform about the specific needs for reaching the 
				    acceptable standards of child's lifes. They are also able to create the necessary projects that will walk 
				    them through the path to follow the standards. Through our portal, individuals and 
				    organizations know about child's needs, projects and their status. 
				    This information is critical for participants that are able to decide 
				    in detail how their contribution is used and know how their volunteer actions will make 
				    a difference. It is also important for nonprofits willing to help to the cause in their 
				    specific area. Therefore, our portal creates a network connecting orphanages with 
				    organizations, individuals and nonprofits with different expertise. A collaborative 
				    environment results in a more efficient support and increases the confidence of people 
				    participating to the cause. In addition, we hope our portal will be a site to share 
				    knowledge that allows new projects to learn from previous experience. Moreover, it will 
				    be a practical source of information for volunteers and organizations. We intend to use 
				    the resources in each area provided by existing organizations to support existing 
				    projects.  
		  		    </td>
	  		    </tr>
	  		    <tr>
	  		    	<td>
	  		    	Our organization provides the technoligical tools, consultancy and expertise to support 
				    activities toward these goals in various areas. Our portal is a visual 
				    development solution for organizations and projects to increase contributions from 
				    individuals and support improving the standards of life of children around the world 
				    by addressing the current issues:
			
			  		<UL TYPE="SQUARE">
			  			<li>Joining efforts and resources to take advantage of previous experiences</li>
			  			<li>Motivating collaboration against competition</li>
			  			<li>Informing more contributors about the status of the projects</li>
			  			<li>Allowing contributors to make decision on how their help is used</li>
			  			<li>Rewarding contributors to motivate more collaboration</li>
			  			<li>Creating a strong network of resources working together on the common objective of improving the life quality of orphaned and abandoned children.</li>
			  			<li>Creating a network of volunteers, motivate people to participate in the program and facilitate their experience</li>
			  			<li>Improving the relationship and links between donors, non-profit organizations and volunteers.</li>
			  			<li>Increasing the help to orphaned and abandoned children</li>
			  			<li>Increasing the flow of information about the cause</li>
			  			<li>Visually representing the status and the resources for everyone who wants to change the situation.</li>
					</UL>
	  		    	</td>
	  		    </tr>
	  		 </table>
		</div>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 