<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
	xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui">
    <ui:with field='res' type='com.owb.playhelp.client.resources.Resources'/>
    
	<ui:style src="../../../resources/GlobalStyles.css">
		.important {
			font-weight: bold;
		}
		.summary{
	        color:#9152a0;
	        margin: 30px;
	   }
		.description{
	        color:#9152a0;
	        margin: 30px;
	   }
	</ui:style>
	<g:HTMLPanel>
		
	   <div class="{style.description}">
	    <h1>OUR VIEW</h1>
	    
			<table align="left">
	    		<!-- 
	    		<tr>
			        <td width="570">
					<g:Image url='{res.viewWebPic.getSafeUri.asString}' pixelSize="300,300"/>  
		  		    </td>
	  		    </tr>
	  		     -->
	  		     <tr>
			        <td width="570">			        
					<g:HorizontalPanel ui:field='sliderPanel' horizontalAlignment="ALIGN_CENTER" width='100%'/>
			        </td>
	  		     </tr>
	    		<tr>
			        <td width="570">
					Orphanage Without Borders provides a common portal for organization and individuals to 
				    unify their efforts and facilitate contributions to the cause of abandoned children. This site 
				    allows projects of our network to inform about the specific needs for reaching the 
				    acceptable standards of child's lifes. They are also able to create the necessary projects that will walk 
				    them through the path to follow the standards. Through our portal, individuals and 
				    organizations know about child's needs, projects and their status. 
				    This information is critical for participants that are able to decide 
				    in detail how their contribution is used and know how their volunteer actions will make 
				    a difference. It is also important for nonprofits willing to help to the cause in their 
				    specific area. Therefore, our portal creates a network connecting orphanages with 
				    organizations, individuals and nonprofits with different expertise. A collaborative 
				    environment results in a more efficient support and increases the confidence of people 
				    participating to the cause. In addition, we hope our portal will be a site to share 
				    knowledge that allows new projects to learn from previous experience. Moreover, it will 
				    be a practical source of information for volunteers and organizations. We intend to use 
				    the resources in each area provided by existing organizations to support existing 
				    projects.  
		  		    </td>
	  		    </tr>
	  		    <tr>
	  		    	<td>
	  		    	Our organization provides the technoligical tools, consultancy and expertise to support 
				    activities toward these goals in various areas. Our portal is a visual 
				    development solution for organizations and projects to increase contributions from 
				    individuals and support improving the standards of life of children around the world 
				    by addressing the current issues:
			
			  		<UL TYPE="SQUARE">
			  			<li>Joining efforts and resources to take advantage of previous experiences</li>
			  			<li>Motivating collaboration against competition</li>
			  			<li>Informing more contributors about the status of the projects</li>
			  			<li>Allowing contributors to make decision on how their help is used</li>
			  			<li>Rewarding contributors to motivate more collaboration</li>
			  			<li>Creating a strong network of resources working together on the common objective of improving the life quality of orphaned and abandoned children.</li>
			  			<li>Creating a network of volunteers, motivate people to participate in the program and facilitate their experience</li>
			  			<li>Improving the relationship and links between donors, non-profit organizations and volunteers.</li>
			  			<li>Increasing the help to orphaned and abandoned children</li>
			  			<li>Increasing the flow of information about the cause</li>
			  			<li>Visually representing the status and the resources for everyone who wants to change the situation.</li>
					</UL>
	  		    	</td>
	  		    </tr>
	  		 </table>
		</div>
		
		
	   <div class="{style.summary}">
	    <table>
	    		<td>
  					<tr>
		  				<table border="5px solid red" align="center">
					    <tr>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link0">General</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link1">Union</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link2">Recycle Efforts</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link3">Clear Communication</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link4">Learning from Experience</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link5">Facilitate Help</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link6">Community Involvement</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link7">Contribution Recognition</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					        <td width="50">
					        <g:Anchor ui:field="link8">General Involvement</g:Anchor>
					        </td>
					    </tr>
					    </table>
			    	</tr>
			    </td>
	    		<tr>
	    			<td>
	    				<table border="5px solid red" align="left">
						    <tr>
						        <td width="50">
								<g:Image url='{res.missionWebPic.getSafeUri.asString}' pixelSize="300,300"/>
							    </td>
						        <td width="250">
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view0">
								Our ultimate goal is to being able to provide the minimum standards for each of the
							    different areas for orphans and abandoned children all around the world. 
							    For this purpose, we believe that we have also responsibilities toward orphanages, 
							    donors, organizations and volunteers participating to this ambitious project. 
							    Therefore, it is also part of our goals building a good relationship within these four 
							    partners, make communication clear and develop common respect. Our goals include the 
							    need to provide this environment in order to empower our efforts toward helping the 
							    conditions of children. 
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view1">
									<b>Union</b>: Many efforts exist around the world providing good support in 
				  			       different areas. We engage to coordinate these efforts and 
				  			       provide an infrastructure allowing these different organizations close 
				  			       collaboration. We will also provide a common gate for organizations and 
				  			       individuals willing to help the cause.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view2">
									<b>Recycle Efforts</b>: We are responsible of using the current efforts for 
				    		       helping orphan and abandoned children to reach resources including funding, 
				    		       volunteers and training. We do not intend to create a new organization 
				    		       helping directly to the cause but helping to bring forward the work of those 
				    		       organizations that are already involved directly with the orphanages or other 
				    		       activities helping children. We engage to empower their efforts.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view3">
									<b>Clear Communication</b>:  We are responsible of surveying the projects and 
				    		       facilitating the communication between the organizations and individuals 
				    		       through our network contributing to helping children. Information about 
				    		       the status and needs of the projects will be frequent and clear. This will 
				    		       guaranty that the standards of each project are follow and people know at 
				    		       any time the status of their investments. Also, our infrastructure will 
				    		       facilitate the people providing resources such as money or time to decide in 
				    		       what specific project and activity they want to help. For example, donors 
				    		       should be able to decide  to the detail of funding to a health activity 
				    		       such as buying new drugs for an orphanage.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view4">
									<b>Learning from Experience</b>: We aim to create an infrastructure allowing 
				    		       projects to learn from previous and current projects. Therefore, non-confidential 
				    		       information have to be available and organized to increase the efficiency of 
				    		       the projects. We engage to provide tools to the collaborators of each project 
				    		       in order to share information and avoiding repeating the same efforts.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view5">
									<b>Facilitate Help</b>: We engage to build an infrastructure were people can 
				    		       easily provide their help. This will be perform by taking advantage of the 
				    		       current technological advances and bringing them to the organizations, 
				    		       individuals and orphanages. In addition, we will facilitate volunteer 
				    		       opportunities with a minimum expenses.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view6">
									<b>Community Involvement</b>: This experience should be not only a way to improve 
				    		       the quality of life of orphan children but also an example to all involved people 
				    		       as donors, volunteers and staff. We can learn the basic 
				    		       and good principles by focusing on children that have much to teach us and 
				    		       paying attention to the important needs of a human being. We engage to involve 
				    		       the children in project and to provide feedback of their opinions and feelings 
				    		       to the community.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view7">
									<b>Contributor Recognition</b>: Social recognition is an important source of 
				    		       motivation for contributors. We will provide an infrastructure that will 
				    		       facilitate social network recognition and awards to volunteers, donors, 
				    		       organizations and orphanages for their contribution or their good work and 
				    		       participation.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
								<g:HTMLPanel ui:field="view8">
									<b>General Involvement</b>: We aim to involve as many people as possible to help 
				    		       to the cause. For this purpose, it is also part of our involvement to bring the 
				    		       problem of orphan and abandoned children needs to the community. We engage to broadcast the need for 
				    		       helping these children and provide tasks to the community helping for the cause 
				    		       and adapted to each group we are trying to reach to such as schools. 
				    		       Thus, outreach is part of our goals.
							    </g:HTMLPanel>
			    		    	</td>
			    		    </tr>
			    		 </table>
	    			</td>
	    		</tr>
	    	</table>
	    
		</div>
	</g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder> 